const level13Questions = [
 {
        question: "Cửa hàng",
        answers: ["公司 (gōngsī)", "商店 (shāngdiàn)"],
        correct: "商店 (shāngdiàn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Luật sư",
        answers: ["律师 (lǜshī)", "小 (xiǎo)"],
        correct: "律师 (lǜshī)",
    },
    {
        question: "Ngoại thương (danh từ)",
        answers: ["外贸 (wàimào)", "多 (duō)"],
        correct: "外贸 (wàimào)",
    },
  {
        question: "Máy tính",
        answers: ["电脑 (diànnǎo)", "电话 (diànhuà)"],
        correct: "电脑 (diànnǎo)",
    },
    {
        question: "Khăn giấy",
        answers: ["纸巾 (zhǐjīn)", "报纸 (bàozhǐ)"],
        correct: "纸巾 (zhǐjīn)",
    },
    {
        question: "Đồng hồ",
        answers: ["手表 (shǒubiǎo)", "手机 (shǒujī)"],
        correct: "手表 (shǒubiǎo)",
    },
    {
        question: "Bàn chải đánh răng",
        answers: ["牙刷 (yáshuā)", "牙膏 (yágāo)"],
        correct: "牙刷 (yáshuā)",
    },
    {
        question: "Điện thoại",
        answers: ["手机 (shǒujī)", "手表 (shǒubiǎo)"],
        correct: "手机 (shǒujī)",
    },
    {
        question: "Cái tủ",
        answers: ["柜子 (guìzi)", "箱子 (xiāngzi)"],
        correct: "柜子 (guìzi)",
    },
    {
        question: "Kem đánh răng",
        answers: ["牙膏 (yágāo)", "牙刷 (yáshuā)"],
        correct: "牙膏 (yágāo)",
    },
    {
        question: "Máy sấy tóc",
        answers: ["吹风机 (chuīfēngjī)", "洗衣机 (xǐyījī)"],
        correct: "吹风机 (chuīfēngjī)",
    },
    {
        question: "Quần áo",
        answers: ["衣服 (yīfu)", "裤子 (kùzi)"],
        correct: "衣服 (yīfu)",
    },
    {
        question: "Cái bàn",
        answers: ["桌子 (zhuōzi)", "椅子 (yǐzi)"],
        correct: "桌子 (zhuōzi)",
    },
    {
        question: "Được không?",
        answers: ["行不行?", "好不好?"],
        correct: "行不行?",
    },
        {
        question: "Gà trống",
        answers: ["攻击 (gōngjī)", "公鸡 (gōngjī)"],
        correct: "公鸡 (gōngjī)",
    },
];

export default level13Questions;